Norman Corwin Papers
Norman Corwin Papers
- Productions of Corwin
  - Radio programs, individual
    - One World Flight, 1947
      - Recording, No. 12 New Zealand, rehearsal
        - One World Flight: Rehearsal of Program No 12, New Zealand [disc 2 of 2], 04/01/1947; corwin_0067; Lacquer discs/acetates
          YR68490
      - Recording, No. 12 New Zealand, work cuts
        Only copy. Materials from these discs was incorporated in a broadcast over CBS on April 8,1947. "Work Cuts"; disc set includes excerpts of interviews with Prime Minister Peter Fraser, Maori Minister of Native Affairs Tirikatene, housewives, doctors, schoolchildren: also selections by Maori chorus.
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, parts 1 and 2 [disc 1 of 5], 3/27/47; 04/08/1947; corwin_0044; Lacquer discs/acetates
          Side 1: 1 - 12-1; 2 - 12-2; 3 - 12-3; 4 - 12-4; 5 - 12-5; 6 - 12-6; 7 - 12-7; 8 - 12-8; 9 - 12-10; 10 - 12-11; 11 - 12-12; Side 2: 1 - 12-13; 2 - 12-14; 3 - 12-15; 4 - 12-16; 5 - 12-17; 6 - 12-18; 7 - 12-19; 8 - 12-20; 9 - 12-21; 10 - 12-22; 11 - 12-23; 12 - 12-24; 13 - 12-25; 14 - 12-26; 15 - 12-27.
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, parts 3 and 4 [disc 2 of 5], 3/27/47; 04/08/1947; corwin_0045; Lacquer discs/acetates
          Side 1: 1 - 12-23; 2 - 12-29; 3 - 12-30; 4 - 12-31; 5 - 12-32; 6 - 12-33; 7 - 12-34; 8 - 12-35; 9 - 12-36; Side 2: 1 - 12-37; 2 - 12-38; 3 - 12-39; 4 - 12-40; 5 - 12-9; 6 - 12-41; 7 - 12-42; 8 - 12-43; 9 - 12-44; 10 - 12-45
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, part 5 [disc 3 of 5], 3/27/47; 04/08/1947; corwin_0046; Lacquer discs/acetates
          1 - 12-46; 2 -12-47; 3 - 12-48; 4 - 12-49; 5 -12-50; 6 - 12-51; 7 - 12-52; 8 - 12-54; 9 - 12-53
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, part 4 [disc 4 of 5], 3/27/47; 04/08/1947; corwin_0047; Lacquer discs/acetates
          1 - 12-28; 2 - 12-29; 3 - 12-7; 4 - 12-8; 5 - 12-41
      - Recording, No. 12 New Zealand, work cuts
        "Work Cuts"; disc set includes excerpts of interviews with a housewife Mrs. Jeffries and Mr. Thomson
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, parts 1 and 3 [disc 1 of 2], 8/10/46; corwin_0048; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - One World Flight: New Zealand, parts 2 and 4 [disc 2 of 2], 8/10/46; corwin_0049; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, No. 13 Conclusion
        Summary of observations of trip, including much material not heard in previous 12 programs. Includes Edouard Benes, Pandit Nehru, Paul V. McNutt, Philip Noel-Baker.
        - One World Flight: Conclusion [disc 1 of 2], 04/08/1947; corwin_0026; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - One World Flight: Conclusion [disc 2 of 2], 04/08/1947; corwin_0027; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Passport for Adams
      Written, directed, produced by Corwin. The series starred Robert Young as Douglas Adams and Paul Stewart as his photographer-assistant, Quisinberry.
      - Correspondence (75), 1943; includes letters to Robert Young, who starred in it; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Recording, Episode 1: Assignment United Nations
        - Passport for Adams opening program [Assignment: United Nations] [disc 1 of 3], 08/24/1943; corwin_0298; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
        - Passport for Adams opening program [Assignment: United Nations] [disc 2 of 3], 08/24/1943; corwin_0299; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Passport for Adams opening program [Assignment: United Nations] [disc 3 of 3], 08/24/1943; corwin_0300; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, Episode 7: On to Moscow
        Broadcast from hollywood on Sept. 28, 1943, as the seventh of an eight-week series entitled PASSPORT FOR ADAMS. Actual title "On to Moscow." Robert Young and Dane Clark starred. Most of the data and many of the incidents in the program were based on material cabled the previous week from Moscow by Bill Downs, CBS Moscow correspondent.
        - Passport for Adams: Moscow [disc 1 of 3], 09/28/1943; corwin_0316; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Passport for Adams: Moscow [disc 2 of 3], 09/28/1943; corwin_0317; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Passport for Adams: Moscow [disc 3 of 3], 09/28/1943; corwin_0318; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, Episode 6: On to Tel Aviv
        Presented as the 6th program in the series PASSPORT FOR ADAMS over CBS on September 21, 1943. Actual title "On too Tel Aviv." Robert Young was starred as Doug Adams, and Dane Clark appeared as Perry Quisinberry. Aviva was played by Joan Loring. From Hollywood. The program was repeated on May 23, 1944 from New York, with Myron McCormick in the Adams role and Paul Mann as Quisinberry. The author directed both productions. Published among the plays in UNTITLED AND OTHER RADIO DRAMAS. There is note on the sleeve's label that additional data is in Envelope 103. Also there a handwritten note, pointing to the production of May 23, 1944, indicates that the recording is of this production. A handwritten note on the record's label indicates that this is Corwin's copy.
        - Tel Aviv [disc 1 of 2], 05/23/1944; corwin_0155; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
        - Tel Aviv [disc 2 of 2], 05/23/1944; corwin_0156; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    - The People, Yes
      - Correspondence (74), 1941 (Box 20)
      - Manuscript (307), 1941 (Box 20)
      - Recording
        A one-act opera based on the volume by Carl Sandburg, and presented over CBS as the third in the 26 BY CORWIN series. Corwin and Earl Robinson collaborated, the latter having previously been introduced to a national radio audience in Corwin's production of BALLAD FOR AMERICANS two years earlier; later Robinson's LONESOME TRAIN was to have its premiere in the 1944 COLUMBIA PRESENTS CORWIN series. For this production, Everett Sloane and Burl Ives starred. It was Ives' first dramatic singing role on radio. On the sleeve label there is a note that additional data is in Envelope 74. A hand written note on the disc's label indicates that the record is personal property of Norman Corwin.
        - The People, Yes [disc 1 of 2], 05/18/1941; corwin_0104; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - The People, Yes [disc 2 of 2], 05/18/1941; corwin_0105; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Pitch to Reluctant Buyers, Columbia Presents Corwin, Season 1 #20
      - Recording
        Broadcast over CBS on August 1, 1944, as the 20th program in the series COLUMBIA PRESENTS CORWIN. It was one of very few in the series that Corwin did not write himself: it was written by Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee, who later achieved fame with their plays INHERIT THE WIND and AUNTIE MAME, etc. Corwin directed and produced. Martin Gabel was narrator, and others in the cast included Herbert Berghoff, Robert Dryden, Nick Dennis, Paul Mann, Theo Getz, Kermit Murdock, Hester Soundergaard, Lisle Falke, Jack Ayers, Mitzi Gould, Michael Ingram, Kyveli Aliki, Mary Cummings, and Jack Ayers [sic] Music was composed and conducted by Alexander Semmler. On the record label is handwritten in pen "Corwin's copy."
        - Pitch to Reluctant Buyers [disc 1 of 2], 08/01/1944; corwin_0098; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Pitch to Reluctant Buyers [disc 2 of 2], 08/01/1944; corwin_0099; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Plot to Overthrow Christmas
      See also Books: The Plot to Overthrow Christmas and Productions of others: The Congo / The Plot to Overthrow Christmas / Mood Indigo.
      - Correspondence (77), 1938; 1945,; 1962 (Box 20)
      - Recording, 1938 version
        Corwin's first original script for radio. It was presented as the fourth of the WORDS WITHOUT MUSIC series on Christmas Day, 1938. included in the cast were Eric Burroughs as Nero, Arnold Moss as Ivan the Terrible, and Simon Legree, Wiil Geer as the Devil, Don Costello as the Sotto Voce, and Lucille Meredith as Borgia. Published in various editions - one by the Peter Pauper Press, another by Henry Holt & Co. in 1952; also included in the collection THIRTEEN BY CORWIN.
        - The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 1 of 4], 12/25/1938; corwin_0346; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 2 of 4], 12/25/1938; corwin_0347; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 3 of 4], 12/25/1938; corwin_0348; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 4 of 4], 12/25/1938; corwin_0349; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, 1942 version
        In this version, broadcast on December 24, 1942, Benny Rubin played the role of Nero. As heard on the air (though not on the recording), the program was interrupted at about the time when Nero is assigned to assassinate Santa Claus, by a news bulletin announcing the assassination of Admiral Darlan of the Vichy French, in Oran. Script published in the collection THIRTEEN BY CORWIN, and as separate editions by Peter Pauper Press and by Henry Holt in 1952.
        - The Plot To Overthrow Christmas [disc 1 of 2], 12/24/1942; corwin_0177; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
        - The Plot To Overthrow Christmas [disc 2 of 2], 12/24/1942; corwin_0178; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
      - Recording, 1944 version
        On December 19, 1944, Orson Welles appeared as Nero in a production of Corwin's Christmas play, sponsored by Cresta Blanca over CBS. Welles also directed. Corwin had requested Welles to play Nero and also direct, when he sold the rights to Cresta Blanca for this production. He repented of the decision when he heard the broadcast on the opposite coast, for he felt the Welles, for whom he had (and continued to have) great admiration, hammed it up somewhat mercilessly.
        - Orson Welles as Nero in The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 1 of 2], corwin_0218; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Orson Welles as Nero in The Plot to Overthrow Christmas [disc 2 of 2], corwin_0219; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Scripts (77), 1942; 1945; typescript with corrections; final broadcast script (Box 20)
    - Poetic License
      - Correspondence (126), 1937-1938; 1949,; undated (Box 20)
      - Recording
        This broadcast, on Nov. 3, 1938, was most important to Corwin's career, for on the basis of unusually favorable reaction to it, he was given his first series - WORDS WITHOUT MUSIC, which went on the air starting one month later. It marked the first time that poetic material has been brought to radio in this manner. Although in retrospect Corwin considered his techniques crude at this early stage, they contributed to the body of experience that went into the later works. Included in the cast were George C. Coulouris, Arnold Moss, Don Costello, Luis Van Rooten, and Adelaide Klein.
        - Poetic License [disc 1 of 2], 11/03/1938; corwin_0169; Lacquer discs/acetates
          On the disc's label is printed that this recording is property of Columbia Broadcasting System. Also there is a note in pen "C 240"
        - Poetic License [disc 2 of 2], 11/03/1938; corwin_0170; Lacquer discs/acetates
          On the disc's label is printed that this recording is property of Columbia Broadcasting System. Also there is a note in pen "C 241"
    - Psalm for a Dark Year
      - Correspondence (131, 327), 1941-1942; 1946,; 1948 (Box 21)
      - Manuscript (327), 1945; mix of typed and handwritten, with correction (Box 21)
      - Recording
        Originally conceived as a Thanksgiving service, presented as the last of 26 BY CORWIN over CBS on November 9, 1941. The author served as the Principal Voice and co-directed with Joel O'Brien and Perry Lafferty. Alexander Semmler composed and conducted the original choral and orchestral score. Published among the plays in MORE BY CORWIN. Additional data in Envelope 131.
        - Psalm for a Dark Year [disc 1 of 2], 11/09/1941; corwin_0207; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Psalm for a Dark Year [disc 2 of 2], 11/09/1941; corwin_0208; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, "October" by Edwin Gerschefski
        - "October" from "Psalm for a Dark Year", 1969; corwin_0370; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
          Case reads: Setting for women's chorus and organ of "October" from "Psalm for a Dark Year" by Edwin Gerschefski of the University of Georgia 7.5 speed 1969
      - Sheet music, "October" by Edwin Gerschefski, 1969; includes letter from composer (Box 21)
    - Pursuit of Happiness
      - Correspondence (141), 1939 (Box 21)
      - Recording
        Broadcast on the 4:30 pm CBS radio show The Pursuit of Happiness. Donor information: "Original performance starring Paul Robeson with the Lyn Murray chorus and orchestra conducted by Mark Warnow. Music by Earl Robinson, lyrics by John LaTouche. Corwin directed. The ballad was adopted by the Republican party as the musical keynote of its national convention in Philadelphia the following year."
        - Ballad for Americans [disc 1 of 2], November 5, 1939; corwin_0296; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Ballad for Americans [disc 2 of 2], November 5, 1939; corwin_0297; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Radio Primer
      - Correspondence (78, 308), 1941; 1945,; 1957,; 1962 (Box 21)
      - Manuscript (308), 1941; mix of typed and handwritten, with corrections (Box 21)
      - Recordings
        - Radio Primer, 05/04/1941; corwin_0283; series premier; Lacquer discs/acetates
          The opening broadcast of the 26 BY CORWIN series, presented by the Columbia Workshop over CBS on May 4, 1941. Lyn Murray composed and conducted the score. The cast included Frank Gallop, Everett Sloane, Beatrice Kaye, John Brown, Jeanette Nolan, Jack Smart, Hester Sondergaard, and Peter Donald.
        - A Valentine Song, corwin_0371; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 21)
          From label: "Song sent by fan, name unknown, set to Soporific Song from Radio Primer (p. 43 of Thirteen by Corwin)." B side blank.
      - Script (78), 1941; final broadcast script (Box 21)
    - Samson, 26 by Corwin, # 14
      See also Operas: The Warrior.
      - Correspondence (323), 1941; 1957 (Box 21)
      - Manuscript (309) (Box 21)
      - Published, in Theater Arts (309), 1942; first time the magazine ever published a radio script (Box 21)
      - Recording
        Presented as the 14th program of 26 By Corwin on August 10, 1941. Martin Gabel performed the role of Samson, and Mady Christians played Delilah. Bernard Herrmann composed and conducted the original score. The script was the basis of a libretto for the one-act opera THE WARRIOR composed by Bernard Rogers. This opera won the Alice M. Ditson Award and was produced by the Metropolitan Opera Company at the Met in New York City on January 11. 1947. Published in MORE BY CORWIN. Opera libretto published by Fred Rullman, Inc. Text published in Theater Arts Monthly in 1947. On the sleeve's label is a note "Additional data, Envelope 164".
        - Samson [disc 1 of 2], 08/10/1941; corwin_0114; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
        - Samson [disc 2 of 2], 08/10/1941; corwin_0115; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Sandburg, An American Trilogy #1; Columbia Presents Corwin #14
      - Recording
        The first of three programs based on the writing of American literary giants. Corwin adapted poems by Carl Sandburg, drawing most heavily on THE PEOPLE, YES. Charles Laughton, who appeared in each of the three programs, performed the major work, and the score by Bernard Herrmann accompanied. This was the 14th of a series of 22 broadcasts of the firs COLUMBIA PRESENTS CORWIN sequence (there was a second in 1945) and it was presented over CBS on June 6, 1944. The adaptation has not been published. On the sleeve's label is indicated to refer to Envelope #85 for press and mail reaction. A handwritten note on the disc's label indicates that this is Corwin's copy. The printed date there is 06/08/1944, but is crossed off and in pen is written 06/06/1944.
        - American Trilogy 1: Carl Sandburg [disc 1 of 2], 06/06/1944; corwin_0171; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - American Trilogy 1: Carl Sandburg [disc 2 of 2], 06/06/1944; corwin_0172; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Script (85), final broadcast script (Box 21)
    - Savage Encounter, Columbia Presents Corwin, Season 1 #4
      - Correspondence (82), 1944-1945; undated (Box 21)
      - Publicity (82), 1945 (Box 21)
      - Recording
        Presented on March 28, 1944, as the fourth program in the first COLUMBIA PRESENTS CORWIN series. Carl Frank was the Pilot, Joan Alexander played Ara, Arnold Moss was the Native, and Corwin himself played the Prosecutor. Bernard Herrmann composed and conducted and original score. Published as one of the plays in UNTITLED AND OTHER DRAMAS. [On the sleeve's label is written that additional data in Envelope 82. On the disc's label there is a hand written note "Corwin's copy". The recording is not digitized.
        - Savage Encounter [disc 1 of 2], 03/28/1944; corwin_0108; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
        - Savage Encounter [disc 2 of 2], 03/28/1944; corwin_0109; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
      - Script (82), 1944; final broadcast script (Box 21)
    - Seems Radio is Here to Stay
      - Published edition, 1939; privately printed and distributed by CBS; includes numerous woodcut(?) illustrations (Box 21)
      - Recording, Australia production
        Produced by Radio Station 2UE in Sydney, Australia, in November, 1939, under the direction of Bruce Anderson. Minor textual changes were made to correspond to the geographical situation. Originally broadcast under direction of Corwin, over CBS, on April 23, 1939. Published in the collection, THIRTEEN BY CORWIN,Henry Holt, 1942.
        - Seems Radio Is Here To Stay, Oct 1939; corwin_0096; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, original production
        Written, directed, produced by Corwin over CBS on April 24, 1939, Martin Gabel and House Jameson were principal narrators; others in the cast included Arnold Moss, Luis Van Rooten, Alan Devitt, Martin Wolfson, Eric Burroughs, Santos Ortega, Juliana Taberna, Adelaide Klein, Gladys Thornton, Vicki Vola, Sidney Weissman. The score was composed and conducted by Bernard Herrmann. Script published in THIRTEEN BY CORWIN; also, private edition by CBS (in this collection).
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay (original production) [disc 1 of 3], 01/24/1939; corwin_0342; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay (original production) [disc 2 of 3], 01/24/1939; corwin_0343; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay (original production) [disc 3 of 3], 01/24/1939; corwin_0344; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, 1940
        A repeat broadcast of the April 24, 1939 broadcast, with Sir Cedric Hardwicke in the role of Narrator. It was originally narrated by House Jameson. Corwin again directed and produced. He considered this production much inferior to the original. NOT COMPLETE - one or more discs missing. See corwin_0290 for complete copy.
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 1 of 4], 11/11/1940; corwin_0292; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 2 of 4], 11/11/1940; corwin_0293; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 3 of 4], 11/11/1940; corwin_0294; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 4 of 4], 11/11/1940; corwin_0295; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, 1941
        A repeat broadcast of the script originally done on April 24, 1939. This one had the services of Sir Cedric Hardwicke as the narrator, and was broadcast over CBS on February 2, 1941, with the author directing. Corwin rated the production as much inferior to the original. Published in THIRTEEN BY CORWIN, with notes. This is the only copy of the Hardwicke recording in any form.
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 1 of 4], 02/02/1941; corwin_0289; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 2 of 4], 02/02/1941; corwin_0290; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Seems Radio Is Here to Stay [disc 3 of 4], 02/02/1941; corwin_0291; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Script, Australia production (36, 37, 337), 1946; includes cast list, foreword, music royalty information; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Set Your Clock at U-235
      See also Speeches: Set your clock at U-235 and Productions of others: Ryan, Robert.
      - Reprints (102), 1945 (Box 21)
    - So This is Radio
      Corwin wrote, directed and produced. He did not think well of this series, which was conceived by CBS as an outgrowth of the earlier SEEMS RADIO IS HERE TO STAY. Only four of the six broadcasts have survived on records.
      - Correspondence (108), 1939-1940; undated; includes copy of station emergency plan ("Plan Z") with telephone numbers and instructions (Box 21)
      - Program summaries (108), typed summaries or notes for each program (Box 21)
      - Recording, Program No. 1: [topic unknown]
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 1 [disc 1 of 3], 07/24/1939; corwin_0319; part 1 and 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 1 [disc 2 of 3], 07/24/1939; corwin_0320; part 2 and 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 1 [disc 3 of 3], 07/24/1939; corwin_0321; part 3 and 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, Program No. 4: Education
        - So This Is Radio: Education [disc 1 of 2], corwin_0238; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio: Education [disc 2 of 2], corwin_0239; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, Program No. 5: Music
        - So This Is Radio: Music [disc 1 of 2], corwin_0240; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio: Music [disc 2 of 2], corwin_0241; Lacquer discs/acetates
      - Recording, Program No. 6: [topic unknown]
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 6 [disc 1 of 3], 09/29/1939; corwin_0322; parts 1 and 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 6 [disc 2 of 3], 09/29/1939; corwin_0323; part 2 and 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - So This Is Radio Program No. 6 [disc 3 of 3], 09/29/1939; corwin_0324; part 3 and 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Soliloquy to Balance the Budget
      - Correspondence (107), 1941 (Box 22)
      - Manuscript (311), 1941 (Box 22)
      - Script (107), 1941; production script; sound cue sheet (Box 22)
    - Stars in the Afternoon
      - Correspondence (124), 1945; includes two clippings (Box 22)
      - Recording
        Broadcast from Carnegie Hall, New York City, on the afternoon of September 16, 1945, The program was conceived, directed and produced by Corwin at the request of CBS, to preview its product for the 1945-46 season. Among the stars appearing in this program, the framework of which was written by Corwin, were Helen Hayes, Jan Pearce, Artur Rodzinski, Andre Kostelanetz, James Melton, Phil Baker, Bess Myerson, Kate Smith, House Jameson, Patrice Munsel, Edward R. Murrow, Jr., Tom Howard and Earl Wrightson. Unpublished. Additional data in envelope 124. Two of the discs are damaged.
        - Stars in the Afternoon, part 1 of 3, 09/16/1945; corwin_0242; Lacquer discs/acetates
        - Stars in the Afternoon, part 2 of 3, 09/16/1945; corwin_0243; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
        - Stars in the Afternoon, part 3 of 3, 09/16/1945; corwin_0244; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
    - There Will be Time Later, Columbia Presents Corwin #22
      - Correspondence (106), 1944-1945; undated (Box 22)
      - Manuscript (312), 1944; mix of typed and handwritten, with annotations and corrections (Box 22)
      - Scripts (106), 1944-1945; final U.S. broadcast script; heavily annotated broadcast script marked as "Canadian master" (Box 22)
    - They Fly Through The Air, Words Without Music, episode number unknown
      - Correspondence (310), 1939; 1967,; undated; includes original prospectus, photograph of CBS studio audience (Box 22)
      - Manuscript (310), 1939; handwritten, with annotations and corrections (Box 22)
      - Recording